Guide to the Cornell Center for Materials Research records, 1970-2008
Cornell Center for Materials Research records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Center for Materials Research records, 1970-2008
53-24-3676
Cornell University.Materials Science Center.Materials Science Center.
41 cubic feet
Correspondence, Photographs, Publications, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, committee meeting minutes, reports, publications, grant information and subject files pertaining to the Center for Materials Research.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Cornell Center for Materials Research as part of the Materials Research Science and Engineering Centers (MRSEC) program provides support for interdisciplinary materials research and education while addressing fundamental problems in science and engineering that are important to society. The center undertakes materials research of a scope and complexity that would not be feasible under traditional funding for individual research projects or small groups.The mission of CCMR is to advance, explore and exploit the science and engineering of advanced materials. The unifying theme of current research is the study of materials purposefully structured at the nanoscale (near-atomic dimensions) and to be world leaders in the design, control and understanding of the behavior of both crystalline and disordered nanomaterials. This objective is pursued through fundamental experimental and theoretical studies of the assembly and processing of nanomaterials and of their resulting behavior.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, committee meeting minutes, reports, publications, grant information and subject files pertaining to the Center for Materials Research.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; National Science Foundation (U.S.).Materials Research Science and Engineering Centers (Program)
Subjects:
Materials science--Research--United States.; Nanotechnology
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Subseries Ia: Facilities
Subseries Ib: Faculty
Series II. Reports
Subseries IIa: Annual Technical
Subseries IIb: Quarterly
Subseries IIc: Material Science Center Technical Reports and Theses
Subseries IId: Various Other Reports
Series III. Proposals
Series IV. Committees
Subseries IVa: Executive
Subseries IVb: Visiting
Series V. Programs
Subseries Va: Research Experience for Undergraduates
Subseries Vb: Research Experience for Teachers
Subseries Vc: Materials Research Science and Energy Center Subseries Vd: Industry Programs
Subseries Vd: Industry Programs
Subseries Ve: Lectures and Presentations
Series VI. Facilities
Series VII. History of CCMR
Series VIII. General Files
Series IX. Photographs, Slides, Video
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Crystal Preparation- ARPA, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bausch & Lomb Letters to Students, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Student Info, 1960's (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NSF, 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Exchange, Foreign Students, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Extramural Courses, Freshman Work Study Jobs, 1962-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vice President for Research, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vice President for Research, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ARPA, March 1960- June 1967; 7 Folders (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Crystallographic Data Center, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Heart Research, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - MRL Director's List, 1980-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - MSC Newsletter, Color Photos- Annual Report, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dr. Stevens AEC, NASA, 1959-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Electric, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Facilities (Laboratories), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Air Force Office of Scientific Research, 1962-1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - National Science Board, Office of Naval Research, 1973-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - MSC Correspondence- General (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - MSC Correspondence- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Vice President for Research-I, 1973-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vice President for Research-II, 1973-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vice President for Research-III, 1973-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gift for Coore Retirement, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Advanced Computing Equipment-I, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Advanced Computing Equipment-II, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee-I, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee-II, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - W. Van Alan Clark, 1966-1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - MRL Funds, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - DMR 9121654, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - MRSEC Award, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ARPA, July 1967- June 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Info- ARPA, IDL, 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ARPA, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - NYSTAR, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Polymer Outreach- Eastman Kodak, Dupont, Hoecmst Gelanese (1993-'95), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - College of Engineering Interdepartmental Affiliations, 1985-1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - College of Engineering Interdepartmental Affiliations, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - College of Engineering Interdepartmental Affiliations, 1968-1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Interdepartmental Affiliations- Electrical Engineering, 1961-1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Interdepartmental Affiliations- Chemistry, 1980-1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Interdepartmental Affiliations- Chemistry, 1962-1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Interdepartmental Affiliations- Applied and Engg Physics, 1963-1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - MRL Director, 1978-1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Sproull, Sack, 1961-1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Sponsored Program Services Fuel Cell Symposium Info., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report Questions, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - NYSTAR Reports etc., 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - UHV-Stem, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Noel Desch, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NSF Proposed Program on Regional Facilities, NSF Reorganization, 1978, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NSF - I, 1972-1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NSF- II, 1972-1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Interim Report Letters, NSF Programs, 1984-1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NSF Bulletin to MRL's, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Reclassification (CCMR Assistant), Letters of Agreement with CCMR, 2000,2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Directors' Fund, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Cost Sharing, Proposal #0079992, 2000, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Diversity (Includes Articles), 2004, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Board, MRSEC Org., 2000, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - New Members, 2000,2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CCMR Facilities, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - House Science Committee, 2000,2002,2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - MS & E Newspaper, Simmon's Proposal, 2001,2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - CCMR (Miscellaneous), 2001, 2003, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - CCMR Educational Outreach, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - MSC, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Facilities, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - MSC Exec. Committee, 1980, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Capital Equipment, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Unit Review Material and Correspondence, 1982-1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Facility Reports, MSC, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Capital Equipment (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - NSF Review Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Equipment, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Energy (Atomic Energy Commission), 1960-1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Army Research Office, 1964-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Committee Survey of MS & E, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Xerox Fellowship, 1962-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Xerox Corporation, 1969-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sandia Labs, Electric Power Research Institute, MSC Visiting Committee Meeting, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Visiting Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Customs Clearance for Equipment (Electron Microscope), 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Customs Clearance for Equipment (Jeol Model Superprobe), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Customs Clearance for Equipment (Spectrometer Chamber), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Clark Sculpture, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Space & Update, Central Facility/ Research Committee Newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Bard Facilities Report, Cornell Chronicle Article, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Summer Salary, Executive Committee Policy, Start up Funds, 1966-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Projects I (Capital Equipment), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Capital Equipment, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Capital Equipment (& Brookhaven Proposal), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Public Safety, 1971-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Accident Reports, Board of Traffic Control Patents, 1962-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - COLTS (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Polymer Outreach Program, 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Mailing Lists- Polymer Outreach Prog. Participants, Polymer Outreach Program, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - MRL Policy, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Comments on MRL Program Policy Statement, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - REU Correspondence, 1992-2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - ARPA, July 1969-June 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - ARPA, July 1972-June 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Facilities, 1979-2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - REU/RET, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - CCMR SEED, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - CCMR SEED Reviews, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - CCMR SEED Projects, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Clark Hall Space Plans, 1980's (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Duffield Hall Facilities, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Clark Hall Committee, 1968-1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Facility, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Suggested Reviewer's Info, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NSF Info, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Industry Partnerships Info., 2002-2004 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - CCMR Budgets/Capital, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - CCMR Overview, CCMR Charter and History, 1968-2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - MRSEC Outreach Workshop, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - UMV Steam Laboratory (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - CCMR Recerse Site Visit, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - CCMR- Next Grand Renewal Proposal, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Presentation-Agilent Technologies, Jan 2002 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - CCMR Informational Packet, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Interview Schedule- Patrick Govang, Umbach, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - National Research Council- Facilities Study, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - MRSEC Brochure (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - CCMR Publicity- News Clippings, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Subseries Ia: Facilities
  - Geological Sciences, Graduate Students, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - LASSP (Laboratory of Atomic and Solid State Physics), 1965-1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Materials Science and Engineering, 1964-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Physics, Cornell Engineering Quarterly, MS & E Undergraduate Brochure, 1962-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Science, Technology & Society Program, Theoretical & Applied Mechanics, Center Administrative Acct., 1969-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Budget Requests, Revisions Information, Other Funds, Travel Policy, 1966-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Clark Maintenance, 1969-1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Open House File, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Clark Hall Energy Conservation, 1973-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 7th Floor Projection Plan, Clark Hall, Physics-ARPA Building, 1960-1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Clark Hall Building Problems, 1967-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Clark Hall Space Occupancy- I, 1966-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Clark Hall Space Occupancy- II, 1963-1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ARPA Space Allocation, 1961-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Building Furniture, Sproull Funds, 1990, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Space- Baker Laboratory, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Space- Bard Hall, 1967-1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bard Hall Renovation, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Clark Hall X-ray Facility, 1980-1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Mechanical Testing Facility, 1966-1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Materials Preperation, 1982-1995 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fume Hood, Liquid Helium, Microkelvin Facility, 1985-1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Liquifier, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Electronics Facility, Electron Microscopy Facility, 1980-1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Electron Microprobe Facility, Dye Laser Facility, 1977-1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - General MSC Facilities, 1975-1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Central Facilities Capital Equipment, 1977-1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - MSC Central Facilities, 1981-1996 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - MSC Central Facilities- Descriptions, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Polymer Characterization Facility, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Holcomb, 1965-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Excess Govt Equipment, 'Forefronts'-Center for Theory & Simulation in Science & Eng, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - MSC Annual Meetings & GRA Support Requests, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Office Equipment, MSC Dodge Van, 1968-1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Annual Technical Report- Sequence Set-up Instructions and Colour Masters, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - MRL- Early History, Study Groups Proposal Supplement, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Personnel Support Group, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Publishers, 1973-1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence and Inquiry, 1974-1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - MSC Annual Meetings & GRA Support Requests, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Subseries Ib: Faculty
  - Paul Houston, 1985-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chung-Yeun Hui, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Michael Iasaccson, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Malvin Kalos, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Edward J. Kramer, 1967-1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - James A. Krumhansl, 1968-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Atsuo Kuki, 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - David Lee, 1966-1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Che-Yu Li, 1961-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Roger J. Loring, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - James Mayer, 1979-1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - N. David Mermin, 1967-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Robert P. Merrill, 1976-1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - George H. Morrison, 1961-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mark S. Nelkin, 1966-1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Carol Nichols, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Chris Ober, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Yih-Hsing Pao, 1970-1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Jeevak M. Parpia, 1986-1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - S. Leigh Phoenix, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - R.O. Pohl, 1957-1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Cliff R. Pollock, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Daniel C. Ralph, John D. Reppy, 1996-1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Rhodin, 1968-1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Rhodin, 1976-1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Robert C. Richardson, 1968-1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ruoff (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Wolfgang H. Sachse (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Stephen L. Sass, 1967-1997 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - James P. Sethna, 1983-1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Albert J. Sievers, 1962-1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Eric Sigga, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - John Silcox, 1984-1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - John Silcox, 1960-1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Barry Carter, 1979-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Roderick K. Clayton, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Michael Fischer, 1965-1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - David Kohlstedt, 1974-1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Parratt, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bowers, 1961-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Burton, 1960, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Faculty, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cranch, 1961-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Athene Donald, 1982, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Steve Gregory, 1978-1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Robert Hughes, 1965-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Herbert H. Johnson, 1960-1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Herbert Mahr, 1962-1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Porter, 1971-1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - David Seidman, 1966-1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Siegel, 1972-1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sienro, 1974-1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Silsbee, 1971-1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Dotsevi Sogah, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chung L. Tang, 1964-1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Michael O. Thompson, 1984-1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Robert Thorne, 1987-1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Watt W. Webb, 1960-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Watt W. Webb, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Benjamin Widen, 1965-1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - John W. Wilkins, 1965-1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Frank Wise, 1988-1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - George L. Wolga, 1960-1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Peter Wolcanzanski, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Alan T. Zehnder, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - David B. Zax, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Grochala, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dieckmann, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Frank Disalvo, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - T. Michael Duncan, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Eastman, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Elser, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - James R. Engstrom, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Fitchen, 1962-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Carl Franck, 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Jean Frechet, 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Jack Freed, 1962-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Alexander L. Gaeta (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Grannelis, 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - David Grubb, 1978-1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Edward W. Hart, 1977-1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hartman, 1960-1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Chris Henley, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Wilson Ho, 1980-1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Roald Hoffman, 1969-1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hector D. Abruna, 1983-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Andy C. Albrecht, 1961-1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Vinay Ambegaokar, 1961-1982 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Alan Brad Anton, 1984-1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Noel Ashcroft, 1966-1997 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Dieter Ast, 1968-1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Joseph M. Ballantyne, 1964-1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - William A. Bassett, 1986-1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Boris W. Batterman, 1964-1991 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Si B. Bauer, 1968-1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Blakely, 1963-1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Bodenscantz, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Joel Brock, 1988-1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Robert Buhrman, 1972-1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - James Burlitch, 1974-1995 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Chester, 1964-1993 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Paulette Clancy, 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Terrill A. Cool, 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Barbara H. Cooper, 1983-1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Harold Craighead, 1988-1997 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Series II. Reports
  - Subseries IIa: Annual Technical
    - First Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Govt Agency Support to Members of MSC Survey of Govt Agency Support, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - No folder 13 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Annual Technical Report, 1985-86 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Technical Progress Report, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report- Members, Correspondents Included, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee Records, Annual Report, 1997-2005 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Facility Managers' Annual Report (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - MRSEC Annual Report and Continuation Report, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report and Continuation Request, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report and Continuation Request, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report and Continuation Request, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Subseries IIb: Quarterly
    - List of Technical Reports and Publications, May 1965; Jun 1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Quarterly Reports, Sept, Dec 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly Reports, Mar, Jun, Sept 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1967; Mar, Jun, Sept 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1968; Mar, Jun, Sept 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1969; Mar, Jun 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Quarterly Reports, Sept 1971- Mar 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Sept, Dec 1971; Mar, Jun, Sept, Dec 1972; Mar 1973
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept, Dec 1973; Mar 1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept, Dec 1974; Mar 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept, Dec 1975; Mar 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept, Dec 1976; Mar, Jun 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Quarterly Reports, Sept, Dec 1977; Mar, Jun 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Quarterly Reports, Sept, Dec 1978; Mar, Jun 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Quarterly Reports, Sept, Dec 1979; Mar 1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept, Dec 1980; Mar 1981 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept, Dec 1981; Apr 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1982; Mar, Jun, Sept 1983 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1983; Mar, Jun, Sept 1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1984; Mar, Jun, Sept 1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1985; Mar, Jun 1986 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1986, Mar 1987 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1987, Mar 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1988, Mar 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1989, Mar 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1990, Mar 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Dec 1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Quarterly Reports, Mar, Jun 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Quarterly Reports, Sept, Dec 1992; Mar 1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Quarterly Reports, Jun, Sept, Dec 1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Quarterly Reports, Mar, Jun, Sept 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1994; Mar, Jun, Sept 1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1995; Mar, Jun, Sept 1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Quarterly Reports, Dec 1996, Mar 1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)